A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Office of the Vice President, Logistical Services, Office Files of James T. Ivy FA668
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Appendix A: Staff and Consultant Reports in Collection: Administrative
  - A Review of Purchasing Systems and Procedures (first draft) - Ford Foundation, 1978 November (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Access to Ford Foundation Records: Policy and Procedures - Ford Foundation, 1974 April 4 (Box 2, Folder 12, Report 9278)
  - Affirmative Action and Foundation Grantees - McGeorge Bundy, 1972 November 15 (Report 1994, Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action and Foundation Grantees - McGeorge Bundy, 1973 June 25 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Affirmative Action Policy: Purchase of Goods and Services (draft) - Ford Foundation, 1973 May 31 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Affirmative Action Program for the Employment of Women and Minorities on the Professional Staff of the Ford Foundation: A Review and Analysis (Information Paper) - Ford Foundation, 1974 February (Box 3, Folder 8, Report 1984)
  - Appraisal: Ford Foundation Properties - William J. Gill & Co., 1971 September 9 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Central Secretariat: Modifications in Services - Willard J. Hertz, 1977 May 16 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Comptroller's Office - FY 1976-79 Staffing Costs and Projections (memo, draft) - Kieran M. Bracken, 1975 February 21 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Development Potentials of the Turtle Bay Area of Manhattan - Hammer, Greene, Siler Associates, 1967 March 29 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Discussion Paper on a Real Estate Investment Program - Ford Foundation, 1967 March 20 (Report 5519, Box 5, Folder 8)
  - External Affirmative Action Initiative: A Review of the First 18 Months - Office of the Secretary, 1975 July (Box 3, Folder 9, Report 2028)
  - External Affirmative Action Program - Office of the General Counsel, 1977 October (Report 6215, Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Ford Foundation Communications Facilities during After-Hours, Weekends, and Holidays, 1974 June 4 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Foundation Building - Options (memo) - Arthur D. Trottenberg, 1976 November 9 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Library Handbook - Ford Foundation, 1973 August (Report 9291, Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Logistical Services -- A Case for Reorganization (memo, draft) - S.S. Mistretta, 1973 August 31 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Management Costs Paper - Personnel Services Section (memo, draft) - William P. Gormbley, 1975 February 13 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Minority Suppliers and Equal Employment Opportunity (memo) - James R. Farrell, 1972 January 3 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Organizational Structure and Basic Functions of the Office of Logistical Services, Division of Administration - Ford Foundation, 1979 April (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Personnel Services Circa 1979 (memo) - William P. Gormbley, 1975 February 11 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Preliminary Investment Analysis: Beaux Arts Hotel - John R. White - James D. Landauer Associates, Inc., 1968 April 1 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Proposal for United Nations Area Planning - Ford Foundation, 1968 November 25 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Proposed Overseas Compensation Package (final draft), 1977 May 20 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Proposed Overseas Compensation Package (memo) - Arthur D. Trottenberg, 1977 June 10 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Proposed Real Estate Development Program - Ford Foundation, 1967 June 23 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Real Estate Investment in the United Nations Area - McGeorge Bundy, 1967 January 19 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Recommendation for the Disposal of Second Avenue Properties, 1976 October (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Records Services - Organizational Relationships (memo, draft) - S.S. Mistretta, 1973 August 22 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Report on Field Office Reporting Requirements - Robert A. Mayer, 1972 August 31 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Report on the Future Development of the Library - Jane Franck, 1968 December 17 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Retrenchment in Management Costs: Shopping List (memo) - James T. Ivy, 1974 April 30 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Retrenchment of Management Costs - David E. Bell, 1975 February 21 (Report 8998, Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Retrenchment of Management Costs (draft) - Education and Research Division, 1975 February 12 (Box 3, Folder 14, Report 9184)
  - Retrenchment of Management Costs: A Progress Report - Ford Foundation, 1975 March (Box 4, Folder 4, Report 9184)
  - Retrenchment of Management Costs: An Interim Progress Report (draft) - Ford Foundation, 1975 March 4 (Box 3, Folder 12, Report 9184)
  - Retrenchment of Management Costs: Office of the Secretary and General Counsel (memo) - Howard R. Dressner, 1975 February 19 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Retrenchment of Management Costs: Progress Report II - Ford Foundation, 1976 March (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Retrenchment Projections - Office of Logistical Services, 1975 January (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Retrenchment Projections - Office of Logistical Services, 1975 March (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Review of Volume of Activity in Certain Units of the Office of Logistical Services - James T. Ivy, 1977 March 22 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Salary Policy for 1975 (memo) - Arthur D. Trottenberg, 1974 September 6 (Box 1, Folder 14, Report 10932)
  - Special Retrenchment Fund (memo) - Arthur D. Trottenberg, 1975 May 7 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Stechert Hafner Project - Jane Franck, 1974 June 6 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Study of Ford Foundation Library Services - Peter Zabriskie, 1976 April (Box 2, Folder 9, Report 5521)
  - The Control of the Foundation's Mail: Procedures, Problems, and Prospects - Eldon L. Jones, 1976 February 6 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - The Division of Administration: A Thumbnail Sketch - James T. Ivy, 1979 April (Box 1, Folder 9, Report 5116)
  - The Ford Foundation Logistical Services Department: Operating Cost Comparison - James R. Farrell, 1973 May 31 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - United Nations Development Corporation: Market Study for Proposed Hotel - Harris, Kerr, Forster and Company, 1970 September (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Appendix B: Staff and Consultant Reports in Collection: Programmatic
  This appendix lists staff and consultant programmatic reports that can be found within the collection. The list is alphabetical by title.
  - Report of the Board of Trustees of the United Nations International School - Board of Trustees, UNIS, 1971 November (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - United Nations International School: Historical Background on Ford Foundation Involvement (Box 4, Folder 7)